[{"question":"Which is the only mammal that canâ€™t jump?","optionA":"Dog","optionB":"Elephant","optionC":"Goat","optionD":"Lion","answer":"Elephant"},{"question":"The largest country in the world is","optionA":"The United States","optionB":"India","optionC":"Japan","optionD":"Russia","answer":"Russia"},{"question":"The largest river in the world is","optionA":"Nile","optionB":"Ganga","optionC":"Amazon","optionD":"Yangtze","answer":"Nile"},{"question":"The Largest Desert in the World","optionA":"Sahara","optionB":"Taar","optionC":"Antartic","optionD":"Arabian","answer":"Antartic"},{"question":"The Largest Continent in the World","optionA":"Africa","optionB":"Asia","optionC":"Europe","optionD":"North America","answer":"Asia"},{"question":"The Largest Airport in the World","optionA":"Beijing Airport","optionB":"Los Angeles Airport","optionC":"Atlanta Airport","optionD":"Tokyo Airport","answer":"Atlanta Airport"},{"question":"The Largest Ocean in the World","optionA":"Atlantic Ocean","optionB":"Indian Ocean","optionC":"Pacific Ocean","optionD":"Southern Ocean","answer":"Pacific Ocean"},{"question":"The Largest Animal in the World","optionA":"Elephant","optionB":"Whale","optionC":"Girafee","optionD":"Camel","answer":"Whale"},{"question":"Which is the Capital of India","optionA":"Delhi","optionB":"TamilNadu","optionC":"AndraPradesh","optionD":"Maharastra","answer":"Delhi"},{"question":"Where is Gateway of India Located","optionA":"Mumbai","optionB":"Chennai","optionC":"Delhi","optionD":"Kolkata","answer":"Mumbai"},{"question":"Who is the current World Champion in MotoGp","optionA":"Marc Marques","optionB":"Valentino Rossi","optionC":"John Mir","optionD":"Dani Pedrosa","answer":"John Mir"},{"question":"Which cricketer is know as Master-Blaster","optionA":"Rohit Sharma","optionB":"Virat Kohli","optionC":"MS Dhoni","optionD":"Sachin Tendulkar","answer":"Sachin Tendulkar"},{"question":"Who lifted the Cricket World Cup in 2011","optionA":"India","optionB":"Australia","optionC":"South Africa","optionD":"New Zealand","answer":"India"},{"question":"Which country has powerfull army force in the world","optionA":"India","optionB":"China","optionC":"U.S","optionD":"Russia","answer":"U.S"},{"question":"Which stadium is Considered as World;s Largest in the World","optionA":"Motera Stadium","optionB":"Wankadae Stadium","optionC":"MA Chidambaram Stadium","optionD":"Eden Garden Stadium","answer":"Motera Stadium"}]